Office of the Vice Provost Records UA166
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- 2017 accessions, circa 1980 -- 2016; UA166.003; 46.8 Linear Feet
  - May 2017 accession, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.001; 13.2 Linear Feet 11 record cartons
    - Gilchrest, Barbara: NIH, Sequential Activation of Melanocyte Differentiation Genes, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Najjar, Victor: Public Health Service, Tissue Enzymes and Plasma Proteins, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 4-5)
    - Norris, Lonnie: Linz Institute, Inc., Lornoxicam, a Therapeutic Dose Range Finding Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Norris, Lonnie: McNeil Consumer Products Company, A Double-Blind, Multi-Clinic Single Dose Evaluation of the Comparative Analgesic Efficacy of Aspirin 1000mg/Caffeine 64mg, Ibuprofen 400mg and Placebo in the Treatment of Post-Operative Pain Following Third Molar Extraction, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00006; 2 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 7-8)
    - O'Brien, Kevin: Faulkner Hospital, Study of Bronchitis in Cocaine Users and Controls, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - O'Callaghan, Michael: Boehrenger-Ingelheim, Scintigraphic Evaluation of Equine Pulmonary Function in the Normal and Diseased State, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Ofner, Peter: National Cancer Institute, Prostatic Differentiation and Sex Hormone Metabolism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Ofner, Peter: National Science Foundation, Prostatic Androgen Metabolism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 12-13)
    - Ofner, Peter: National Cancer Institute, Androgens in Prostatic and Epidydimal Culture, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00011; 2 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 14-15)
    - Seeherman, Howard: Genzyme, Efficacy of Intra-Articular Hyaluronate in the Production of Post-Operative Synovitis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - Seeherman, Howard: Bristol Laboratories, Hyaluronic Acid Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Sedgwick, Charles: Association of Avian Veterianarians, Development of a Technique to Utilize Metabolic Scaling for the Determination of Appropriate Drug Regimens in Birds, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Schwartz, William: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Studies in the Detection and Deterrence of Medical Malpractice, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Schwartz, Edith: Pfizer, Effect of Piroxicam on Surgically Induced Osteoarthritis in the Knees of Guinea Pigs, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 20)
    - Snydman, David: NIH, Transfusion Transmitted CMV Prevention in Neonates, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00017; 2 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 21-22)
    - Smulow, Jerome: Gillette Company, Study to Compare Effectiveness of an Electric Toothbrush, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 23)
    - Sonenshein, Abraham: NIH, Role of RNA Polymerase in Bacterial Differentiation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.174.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 174, Folder 24)
    - Sonenshein, Abraham: NIH, Initiation of RNA Synthesis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Soto, Ana: NSF, Purification of a Specific Inhibitor of Estrogen Sensitive Cell Proliferation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, William: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Analysis of Policy Issues Impacting on the Future of Medical Care, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Schwartz, William: DHHS, Malpractice and the Surplus-Line Physicians, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Schwartz, William: Pew Trust, Understanding and Influencing the Malpractice Problem, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Sczekan, Melanie: Medical Foundation, Intracellular Distribution and Subunit Composition of the Vacuolar H+-ATPases in Madin Darby Bovine Kidney Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Schwartz, William: G.D. Searle & Co., Health Care Costs in the Year 2000: The Range of Uncertainty and the Implications for Public Policy, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz, William: Health Care Financing Administration, Response of Massachusetts Acute Care Hospitals to the Massachusetts Cost Containment Act (Chapter 372 of the General Laws), 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz, William: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Policy Options to Contain Health Care Costs, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Krinsky, Norman: Eye Research Institute of the Retina Foundation, Boston, Foveal Pigmentation and Structure: Function and Roles, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Krinsky, Norman: National Cancer Institute, Comparative Absorption and Metabolism of Carotenoids, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Krinsky, Norman: NIH, Fat Soluble Micronutrients in Human Plasma and Tissues, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00012; 2 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 12-13)
    - Kronman, Joseph: American Association of Orthodontists Foundation, Anatomical Basis of TMJ Dysfunction, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Kronman, Joseph: Societe Endo Technic, Canal Finder Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Kugel, Gerard: NIDR, Nitrous Oxide and the Hypothalamic Control of Reproduction, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Kugel, Gerard: DenMat, Evalutation of the Dentinal Bonding Syste, Tenure, With a Composite Restoration of Root Surface Caries After Chemo-Mechanical Caries Removal, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Lawler, Jack: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Cloning and Sequencing of Human Thrombospondin, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Leape, Lucian: The Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, Assessment of Humanistic Qualities of Medical School Applicants, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Leav, Irwin: NIEHS, Transgenic Models for Mutagenesis and Carcinogenesis Testing, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - Leav, Irwin: DHHS, Minority High School Student Research Apprentice Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - Lechleiter, James: NIH, Peptidergic Control of Preocular Tear Film Secretion, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - Krinsky, Norman: FDA, Eighth International Symposium on Carotenoids, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - Leskowitz, Sidney: NIH, Immunological Aspects of Disease, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - Leskowitz, Sidney: NIH, Cellular Aspects of Tolerance and Delayed Hypersensitivity, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00024; 2 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 25-26)
    - Najjar, Victor: March of Dimes Birth Defects Foundation, Threonyl-Lysyl-Prolyl-Agrinine, The Phagocytosis Stimulating Peptide: Its Metabolism in Congenital Familial and Acquired Deficiency States, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 27)
    - Levine, Howard: Massachusetts Centers of Excellence Corporation, Use of a Direct Drug Delivery System in the Treatment of Bovine Mastitis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00026; 2 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 28-29)
    - Kronman, Joseph: Septodont, Local Anethesia with Intraosseous Injections, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.175.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 175, Folder 30)
    - Barach, Howard: Massachusetts Department of Public Health, Dental Services, State Schools, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00001; 4 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 1-4)
    - Barach, Howard: Department of Mental Retardation, Service Contract, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Barach, Howard: Massachusetts Department of Public Health, Danvers State Hospital, Dental Services, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 6-7)
    - Barach, Howard: Department of Mental Health, State Contracts, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00004; 2 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 8-9)
    - Barach, Howard: Department of Mental Health, Metropolitan State Hospital Dental Contract, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00005; 2 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 9-10)
    - Krinsky, Norman: DHHS, Anticarcinogenic Mechanisms of Carotenoid Pigments, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Kraus, Karl: Organogenesis, Inc., The Use of a Synthetic Collagen Tendon Wrap for Repair of the Common Calcanean Tendon in Rabbits, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Krinsky, Norman: National Foundation for Cancer Research, Relationship Between Carotenoids and Retinoids as Anticarcinogenic Agents, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Krinsky, Norman: Environmental Protection Agency, In Vivo Analysis of UV-B Photooxidations, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Rosenberg, Naomi: NIH, Immunoglobulin Genes in Differentiating B Cells, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Rosenberg, Naomi: American Cancer Society, RNA Tumor Virus - Hematopoietic Cell Interaction, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Rosoff, Philip: NIH, Isolation of the Human T Cell Pertussis Toxin Receptor, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Rosoff, Philip: Pew Trust, Biochemical Characterization of the Pertussus Toxin Receptor: A New Growth Factor Receptor in Human T Lymphocytes, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Rossignol, Philippe: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, Determination of Peptidoglycan Degrading Enzymes in Mosquito Salivery Glands and Malaria Sporozoites by Fast Atom Bombardment Mass Spectrometry, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Rosoff, Philip: NIH, Purification of Mitogen-Stimulated Ca+ Transporter, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 20)
    - Rosenwasser, Lanny: NIH, The Immunology of the Vascular Endothelum in Vasculitis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Linda: Morris Animal Foundation, The Effect of Hypertension on Renal Function in Naturally Ocurring Renal Disease in the Dog, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 22)
    - Rowell, Steven: Pitman-Moore, Inc., Compatability of Feline Calici, Herpes, Panleukopenia and Feline Luklemia in a Combination Vaccine, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 23)
    - Rubin, Beverly: Harvard University, Opiate Regulation and Involvement in Maternal Behavior, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.176.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 176, Folder 24)
    - Albertini, David: NSF, Flourescence Microscopy Studies on the Function of Coated Vesicles, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Albertini, David: March of Dimes Birth Defects Foundation, Reproductive Hazards in the Workplace, Home, Community and Environment Research Grants, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Albertini, David: Serono Laboratories, Inc., Multiparameter Cytological Evaluation of Human Oocytes Using Digital Flourescence Imagine Microscopy, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Alroy, Joseph: National Insitute of Neuro. Disorders and Stroke, GM-1 Gangliosidosis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Cheryl: Muscular Dystrophy Association, Hyaluronate-Cell Surface Interactions During Normal and Dystrophic Skeletal Myogenesis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Arbree, Nancy: Scodenco, Overdenture Attachments: A Pilot Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - Auron, Philip: Whitaker Health Sciences Fund, The Identification, Characterization and Molecular Cloning of a T Cell Receptor Site for Interleukin 1, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Lynne, Ausman: University of Massachusetts: Lowell, Effect of Varying Levels of Dietary Cholesterol on Lipoprotein Concentrations and Metabolisms of Monkeys Fed the Average American Heart Association Step 1 Diet, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 8)
    - Schwartz, Robert: National Cancer Institute, Experimental Leukemogenesis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00009; 3 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 9-11)
    - Schwartz, Edith: NIH, Metabolism of Osteoarthritic Articular Cartilage, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 12-13)
    - Schwartz, Edith: Foundation for Nutritional Advancement, Effects of Ascorbic Acid on Metabolism of Matrix Proteins in the Guinea Pig Model of Osteoarthritis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 14)
    - Schwartz, Edith: NIH, Vitamin C Effect on Surgically Induced Osteoarthritis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00012; 2 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 15-16)
    - Bullock, Leslie: NICHD, Androgen Action: Regulation and Mechanism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 17)
    - Bullock, Leslie: Mark Morris Animal Foundation, Study and Treatment of Mammary Tumors in Cats and Dogs, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 18)
    - Bullock, Leslie: Mark Morris Animal Foundation, Feline Hyperthyroidism: Etiology and Pathogenesis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 19)
    - Cantley, Lewis: NIH, Harvard Center for the Study of Kidney Disease, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 20)
    - Cantley, Lewis: American Heart Association, Established Investigatorship Award, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 21)
    - Cantley, Lewis: NIH, Structure and Mechanism of Membrane Transport Systems, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 22)
    - Cantley, Lewis: NIH, Characterization of Phosphatidylnositol Kinase, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.177.00019; 2 Folder(s) (Box 177, Folder 23-24)
    - Cantley, Lewis: NIH, Role of Phosphatidylinositol-3-P in Growth Regulation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Cantley, Lewis: NIH, Mechanism of Cation Transport Regulation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Corey, Seth: NIH, Biochemical Mechanisms of Gm-CSF Priming of Neutrophils, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Cooper, Amiel: NIH, Structure and Synthesis of Leukemic Plasma Membranes, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Cook, William: Jockey Club/Grayson Research Foundation, Exercise-Induced Pulmonary Hemorrhage in the Racehorse: Determination of Cause, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Conrad, Chester: American Heart Association, Myocardial Elastic Properties in Hypertrophy and Fibrosis, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Coffin, John: National Cancer Institute, Relationship of Avian Tumor Virus RNA and Host Genome, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - Coffin, John: NIH, Small Instrumentation Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Coffin, John: Micromol, Avian Vaccine Preparation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Coffin, John: NIH, Mechanisms of Variability of Tumor Virus DNA, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - Coffin, John: NIH, Identification of an Avian Retrovirus Receptor, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Papaioannou, Virginia: USDA, Development and Viability of Micromanipulated Preimplantation Pig Embryos, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - Papaioannou, Virginia: NIH, Embryo Viability as Assessed by ICM/Trophectoderm Ratio, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - Papaioannou, Virginia: NIH, Role of Trophectoderm Subpopulations in Implantation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 14)
    - Papas, Athena: Universit of Lowell Research Foundation, Greater Lowell AHEC Geriatric Dental and Dental Hygeine Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 15)
    - Papas, Athena: West Suburban Elder Services, Inc., Dental Screening, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 16)
    - Papas, Athena: Central Massachusetts AHEC, Geriatric Dental Evaluation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 17)
    - Papas, Athena: Educational Foundation of America, A Comprehensive Oral Health Program for Elders, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 18)
    - Papas, Athena: Southeastern Massachusetts Area Health Education Center, Dental Student Externship Training Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 19)
    - Park, James: NIH, Molecular Biology of Basic Cell Functions, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 20)
    - Pincus, Stephanie: NIH, Cellular Interactions: Lymphocytes and Eosinophils, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 21)
    - Rosenberg, Irwin: NIH, Absorption of Monoglutamyl and Polyglutamyl Folates, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 22)
    - Kronman, Joseph: National Patent Dental Products, Inc., Bond Strength Testing, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 23)
    - Soto, Ana: W. Alton Jones Foundation, Testing of Commonly Used Pesticides and Related Compounds for Estrogenicity, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 24)
    - Gans, Bruce: National Institute on Disability and Rehabilitation Research, Medical Rehabilitation Research and Training Center, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 25)
    - Kirker-Head, Carl: Hoechst Roussel Agrivet, The Efficacy of Propentofylline in the Treatment of Equine Navicular Disease, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 26)
    - Kirker-Head, Carl: Hoechst Roussel Agrivet, Local and Systemic Compatability of a Hyaluronic Acid Drug Intended for Intraarticular Administration in the Horse, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 27)
    - Kirker-Head, Carl: Hoechst Roussel Agrivet, Evaulation of a Hyaluronic Acid Drug for the Treatment of Experimentally Induced Synovitis in the Horse, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 28)
    - Kirker-Head, Carl: Medical Laser Research and Development Corporation, Laser Enhancement of Bone Healing in Rabbits - Preliminary Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 29)
    - Kirker-Head, Carl: Genetics Institute, Heterotopic Implantation of Bone Morphogenic Protein in Sheep, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 30)
    - Cohen, Joseph: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, Chronic Disease Project, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 31)
    - Rubin, Clinton: U.S. Army, Training, Muscle Fatigue, and Stress Fractures, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.178.00032; 2 Folder(s) (Box 178, Folder 32-33)
    - Rubin, Clinton: The Whitaker Foundation, Regulation of Bone Mass by Electromagnetically Induced Electric Fields, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Leav, Irwin: NIH, Small Instrumentation Program, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - North, Thomas: Morris Animal Foundation, Generation and Characterization of Lymphoid Cell Lines from Normal and Immunodeficient Foals, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Madoff, Morton: Boston Foundation, Evaluation of School Based Primary Health Care Services, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Gorbach, Sherwood: NIH, TUSM & Associated Sites Contract, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - Shader, Richard: NIH, Training Award, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - Shader, Richard: Greater Boston Council on Alcoholism, Study of Prevention and Early Intervention of Alcholism, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Stranova, Tom: Commonwealth of Massachusetts, Lemuel Shattuck Nursing Contract, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00008; 2 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 8-9)
    - Farnham, Betsy: VA Medical Center, Medical Specialist Services, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00009; 2 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 10-11)
    - Stranova, Tom: VA Medical Center, Diagnostic Radiology Services, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00010; 2 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 12-13)
    - Kently, Donna: N/A, Assignment to VA Hospital, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - King, Joan: IBM, Interactive Video Training Modules, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - Goldman, Melvin: N/A, Misc., 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - Banks, Henry: DHHS, Clinical Research Center, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - Barrett, Kathleen: NIH, NEMC Agreement, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - Balkovic, Edward: Amicon, Proposal for the Concentration and Purification of Viruses of Veterinary Imporatance Using Cellufine Sulfate, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 19)
    - Loew, Franklin: DHHS, NIH Equipment Grant, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 20)
    - Byrne, Joseph: N/A, Agreements, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 21)
    - Selsing, Erik: Brandeis University, Immunity in Transgenic Mice, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 22)
    - O'Callaghan, Michael: Bioflex Corporation, Effects of Magnetic Pads on Blood Flow to the Distal Limb in the Horse, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 23)
    - Rowan, Andrew: N/A, Misc., 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 24)
    - Gilchrest, Barbara: Shiseido Corporation, Melanogenesis Study, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 25)
    - Haber, Jerome: National Institute of Dental Research, Diabetes and Periodontis Microbiology and Immunology, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Garcia, Raul: VA Medical Center, Aging and Avelor Bone Loss, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 27)
    - Furie, Barbara: NEMC, Membrane Proteins in Blood Coagulation, 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00025.000001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 26)
    - Papas, Athena: N/A, Misc., 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00025.000002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, Joseph: N/A, Misc., 1980 -- 1989; UA166.003.179.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 179, Folder 29)